competify.in 2016-02-14

# Privacy Policy | Competify

 We respect the privacy of everyone who visits this website. As a result we would like to inform you regarding the way we would use your personal data. We recommend you to read this privacy policy so that you understand our approach towards the use of your personal data. 

By submitting your personal data to us, you will be treated as having given your permission – where necessary and appropriate – for disclosures referred to in this policy.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website or mail us at [contactus@competify.in](mailto:contactus@competify.in)

**Scope**

This statement applies to Competify's contents, services and websites.

  * Competify.in collects personal information when you register for a Competify.in service or otherwise voluntarily provide such information. We may combine personal information collected from you with information from other Competify.in services or third parties to provide a better user experience, including customizing content for you.
  * Competify.in uses cookies and other technologies to enhance your online experience.

**Information collection and use**

 We offer a number of services that require you to register for an account or provide any personal information to us. In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information:

Competify.in collects personally identifiable information (such as your name, email address and your facebook and twitter profile pictures) when you register for an personalized account or when you use certain products or services provided by our site. For use of some specific services, providing some specific personally identifiable information shall be compulsory/ mandatory.

Competify.in may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our search technology, customized content and advertising.

This Privacy Policy applies to Competify.in contents and services only. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as search results or links from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.

In addition, when you use Competify.in services, you may make some of your personal information public. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return and Competify site will not be responsible for the use or misuse of such information.

Email communication that you send us via the email links on the Site may be shared with company representatives, partners or employees. From time to time, we may send you service-related emails, such as a welcome email when you come in touch with the Site.

**We use your email address to send you:**

  * Special offers
  * News letters
  * Changes in the service's policy or terms of use
  * Event based communications such as new event information, invites, reminders etc. 

**We use your personal information to:**

  * help us provide personalized features
  * tailor our sites to your interest
  * to get in touch with you in the case of policy changes
  * to provide the services requested by you
  * to preserve social history as governed by existing law or policy

**  Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  Competify.in will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.

**  Cookies**

Competify.in may set and access Competify.in cookies on your computer and you may not be able to disable these cookies. Competify.in ensures that all information collected and accessed by Competify.in through the access of these cookies will be maintained in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Competify.in allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one.

**  Affiliated Website**

Competify.in may offer some services in connection with other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to us in order to deliver the service. We process such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  

From time to time we may make changes to this privacy policy. If we make any substantial changes to this privacy policy and the way in which we use your personal data we will post these changes on this page and will do our best to notify you of any significant changes. Please check our privacy policy on a regular basis.  

### **Keeping our records accurate**

We aim to keep our information about you as accurate as possible. If you would like to review, change or delete the details you have supplied us with, please contact us as set out below.

We use personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.
